http://www.fahouryink.com/privacy-policy/

PRIVACY POLICYThanks for visiting FahouryInk.com! Here’s how we collect, use and handle the personal information of visitors to our website.What & why FahouryInk.com does not collect personal information such as your name, postal or email address, except when such information is voluntarily provided by you through our website. Whether you provide any information is 100% up to you.By filling out forms on FahouryInk.com, you are agreeing to receive communications about our services. You always have the opportunity to opt-out of these email communications by unsubscribing.FahouryInk.com does collect non-personally identifiable aggregate information about visitors to our site. This information is used for analytical and statistical purposes and includes data such as a visitor’s host name, internet protocol (IP) address, date, time and duration of your visit, traffic pattern, and related site information. We may use this information to tailor your online user experience on FahouryInk.com.Fahoury Ink will use the information you provide on FahouryInk.com for the purpose of lead generation. Fahoury Ink does not sell or rent personal information collected through FahouryInk.com to anyone or share your individual profile with other third parties (unless requested to do so to comply with legal requests or investigations). However, Fahoury Ink does share your information in aggregate form only.Cookies Fahoury Ink may use “cookies” to collect information about your use of our site. A cookie is a text file that is sent to a browser from a website and stored on a computer’s hard disk. Cookies record information about a visitor to a website, the pages visited, date of the visit, and any preferences that may have been set while the visitor was browsing the site. This information may be used by Fahoury Ink, now or in the future, to tailor your access to certain features, customization of content, or to analyze your activity and behavior on FahouryInk.com. Cookies cannot retrieve any other data from your hard drive, obtain your email address or read cookies created by other websites. The browser only allows the website that created the cookie the ability to access it.If you are concerned about the use of cookies, you may set your web browser options to notify you when a cookie is saved to your computer or to disallow cookies. Prohibiting the use of cookies may restrict your access to certain types of content or features.Links to other sites FahouryInk.com may contain links to client, partner or other third-party sites. Fahoury Ink is not responsible for the privacy practices of or any content on any of these third-party sites, and encourages you to review their privacy policies in detail.Security FahouryInk.com uses industry standard security measures to help protect any personally identifiable information that is temporarily stored on our site. However, data transmission over the Internet is not secure, so we cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to us or receive from us, including information provided via email.Children FahouryInk.com does not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from children under the age of 13. Kids should always ask parents for permission before providing personal information to any site. We urge parents and guardians to play an active role in their children’s use of online resources and to teach them how to safeguard their personal information.We reserve the right to update this Privacy Policy at any time. Therefore, it is recommended that you review this information on a regular basis. Your continued access and use of FahouryInk.com acknowledges that you understand this Privacy Policy and accept its terms and conditions. If you do not agree with the Privacy Policy, please refrain from visiting our website. Contact us with any questions or concerns about our privacy practices. Fahoury InkPrivacy Policy05.22.2018SearchArchivesJuly 2020May 2020April 2020February 2020January 2020March 2019January 2019November 2018August 2017May 2016CategoriesContent creationContent marketingCreativityMarketing strategy & tacticsSmall businessUncategorized
× Your on-call marketing teamThe owner of a growing business faces relentless demands — selling, servicing, hiring, leading, innovating and oh yeah, marketing.Let’s face it, there’s just not enough time in the day for all those “ings.” But what falls by the wayside most often? Marketing. And the bad news is, you won’t even notice until your phone stops ringing, your website stops converting, and your clients stop buying because they’ve found a new vendor.You’re frustrated because you’re just not ready to bring a marketing director on board. Good news — Fahoury Ink is here to fill the gap. From creating a marketing plan to writing content for your website, we can get you on track and help you stay there. Heck, we can even serve as your complete outsourced marketing department — delivering strategic smarts and creative execution with nary an addition to your head count.Contact us for details on how we’ve helped businesses like yours become better marketers.
